JOHN CHE LARRACUENTE

ENTREPRENEUR + AUDIO & VISUAL CONSULTANT



+202-446-3976



johnchelarracuente@gmail.com



4806 Hayes St NE, Washington DC

Bilingual (Spanish/English) professional with a strong background in creative consulting, translation services, customer service, and income management. Experienced in leading creative workshops, managing accounts + logistics, and ensuring effective communication in diverse environments. Proven ability to enhance customer satisfaction and engagement through dedicated service and attention to detail.

EDUCATION

2008 - 2015

Howard University

Bachelor of Arts in Spanish

Minor: Radio Television & Film

GPA: 3.60

2014

Oaksterdamn University

Indoor Horticulture

Certification: Mastery of Indoor Horticulture

EXPERTISE

- Spanish Language Proficiency
- Conflict Resolution
- Community Organizing
- Stress Management
- Analytical skills
- Critical thinking
- Social Media Management
- Wealth Building Strategies

WORK EXPERIENCE

Audio & Video Consultant

John C Creations LLC, 2015 - Present

- Provided artistic direction, project management, and creative solutions for clients.
- Developed wealth building strategies, and video + audio content for marketing campaigns
- Managed audiovisual (AV) projects, including setup and operation of AV equipment for events, ensuring high-quality presentations and seamless event experiences.
- Collaborated with clients to understand their AV needs, providing customized solutions and technical support.

Supply Chain Specalist

Sweet Greens HQ, January 2022 – January 2024

- Monitored and managed inventory levels, ensuring that all products were accounted for and correctly delivered.
- Maintained detailed records of all deliveries, including time of delivery, condition of products, and customer feedback.

Logistics Coordinator

Capitol City Hydroponics 2017 - 2018

- Maintained high customer satisfaction by delivering to Managed inventory and accepted incoming merchandise.
- Assisted customers and sales associates, handling cashier transactions, returns, and exchanges.
- Maintained organized inventory levels and ensured accurate record-keeping